it's funny because it's so was not going
to be the first the first Apple but I
got talking about it in the last last
video having a production company
step one who doesn't need a production
company it's not it's when we have
millions of members what a production
company that's able to rent out for
cheap ie cost and maintenance film
equipment and editing software for
editing equipment I guess you don't know
if you could rent out editing software
but we can create it and then we can
have it for free that so people are able
to make movies and stories that move
them and so you aren't hopefully that
means that there's more diversity in
film and movies and if we as parents
want more LGBT show us for our children
but just have it in there because kids
are gay and kids have gay parents and
it's ridiculous that most of the media
that's out there is like two-parent
households or no parent households which
is a little weird children unsupervised
seems to be a theme in children shows
and having single parents and aunts
raising them and grandparents or
grandparent Tracy I'm actually probably
happens more often in shows then is
actually real life it's having diversity
of families and diversity of abilities
and having it done in a way hopefully
that is good where the sent it's not the
central theme is that they have two
mommies because who wants to watch that
it's about you know it's paw Patrol but
they just have two mommies it's like
okay cool
you know Ryder and his boyfriend or it's
not a big deal anymore than it's a big
deal to have a young girl you know
marrying a prince have a young princess
marrying Prince it's just commonplace if
you don't meet you know that the central
character is white just like that the
central character is Asian or black or
First Nations like telling the stories
it's not even growing up I'm white I was
raised right although I'm not how to
pretend white I saw diversity as like
the Archie comics that Archie hat you
know had Betty and Veronica and so there
was like a blondes and champions black
hair Shanna brunette and then there was
someone with red hair and it's like
diversity there you go and I felt more
drawn to characters in shows it had red
curly hair like me and so I modeled
myself after characters I think I mean
chicken or egg was I'd like that and
then I just was drawn to those
characters
how could you also look like me I don't
think so I think that I saw out of Green
Gables and Little Orphan Annie and I
happen to have been a lay man and so I
was drawn to them and how artificial is
it that it's a hair color that I was not
able to see myself also I think that's
the overabundance of baby red strong
characters he'd be Longstocking whereas
I didn't see myself so much in the boy
characters or the other white
predominantly characters and so seeing
my mom is because oh my goodness how
important it my speed have amazing
Wonder Woman out there now it only
started a few weeks ago I really want to
put my four-year-old despite the fact
that everyone's like don't bring your
four-year-old stop for a four-year-old
but having a kick-ass female superhero
is for everyone and so maybe a white
toast bit older Timothy but I'm glad it
exists now and how having Asian male
models and black role models and First
Nations role models
and telling their historic stories but
also their make-believe stories it just
happened to focus on them having casting
call that isn't race related if it
doesn't need to be that you're the star
and you get to be um so we need a strong
female lead does it matter what race
they are and see who best fits the role
and so a production company that we all
own and we can create the content
because you create it you would say hey
I have an idea for a story who wants to
come on board and it easily facilitates
collaboration I need someone who could
do this skill and if you're someone who
that speaks to you you're like hey I
have a I have a no trans child I would
love there to be stories out there about
children who are who are trans because
it speaks to like it's directly related
to my child my child needs that content
and your and you have the skill to help
make it you can collaborate and create
something for a fraction the cost you
can crowdsource crowdfund sorry for the
money and created together so that's one
Apple a production company that we all
own together and can share equipment on
and easily collaborate online to come
together and make projects